// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The day on which the Sunâ€™s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called?",
    answer: "The equinox",
    options: [
      "The solstice",
      "The ecliptic",
      "Sunday",
      "The equinox"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who invented the telescope?",
    answer: "Hans Lippershey",
    options: [
      "Elon Musk",
      "Hans Lippershey",
      "Galileo",
      "Johannes Kepler"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many stars in our solar system?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "100",
      "100 billion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the visible part of the Sun called?",
    answer: "the photosphere",
    options: [
      "the photosphere",
      "the atmosphere",
      "the hydrogenosphere",
      "the Sunosphere"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What two motions do all planets have?",
    answer: "orbit and spin",
    options: [
      "rick and morty",
      "rock and roll",
      "orbit and spin",
      "zig and zag"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Approximately how many kilometres are there in a light-year?",
    answer: "9.5 trillion km",
    options: [
      "9.5 km",
      "9.5 million km",
      "9.5 billion km",
      "9.5 trillion km"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the nucleus of a comet made of?",
    answer: "ice, dust, and organic materials",
    options: [
      "fire, dust, and organic materials",
      "ice, dust, and organic materials",
      "water, dust, and organic materials",
      "helium, dust, and organic materials"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When did the race to Space between USSR and USA begin?",
    answer: "1957",
    options: [
      "1945",
      "1948",
      "1957",
      "1963"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "With which US spacecraft did Neil Armstrong and Edwin Aldrin, Jr. land on the moon on 1969?",
    answer: "Apollo 11",
    options: [
      "Apollo 1",
      "Apollo 10",
      "Apollo 11",
      "minecraft 12"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The atmosphere in Mars is mostly composed of:",
    answer: "Carbon dioxide",
    options: [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "H2O",
      "dust"
    ]
  },
  
];